[
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [53, 14, 32, 7, 19],
    "correct_answer": [7, 14, 19, 32, 53],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [40, 30, 55, 10, 25],
    "correct_answer": [10, 25, 30, 40, 55],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [77, 50, 88, 23, 31],
    "correct_answer": [23, 31, 50, 77, 88],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [80, 58, 90, 12, 45],
    "correct_answer": [12, 45, 58, 80, 90],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [21, 41, 18, 5, 27],
    "correct_answer": [5, 18, 21, 27, 41],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [64, 69, 42, 37, 81],
    "correct_answer": [37, 42, 64, 69, 81],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [36, 56, 44, 29, 71],
    "correct_answer": [29, 36, 44, 56, 71],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [57, 11, 63, 8, 22],
    "correct_answer": [8, 11, 22, 57, 63],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [10, 1, 9, 6, 3],
    "correct_answer": [1, 3, 6, 9, 10],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [54, 57, 29, 32, 45],
    "correct_answer": [29, 32, 45, 54, 57],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [30, 25, 60, 15, 20],
    "correct_answer": [15, 20, 25, 30, 60],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [92, 59, 88, 40, 75],
    "correct_answer": [40, 59, 75, 88, 92],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [35, 77, 66, 22, 55],
    "correct_answer": [22, 35, 55, 66, 77],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [53, 59, 41, 33, 70],
    "correct_answer": [33, 41, 53, 59, 70],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [8, 64, 25, 47, 12],
    "correct_answer": [8, 12, 25, 47, 64],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [59, 14, 22, 11, 30],
    "correct_answer": [11, 14, 22, 30, 59],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [66, 54, 38, 19, 25],
    "correct_answer": [19, 25, 38, 54, 66],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de menor a mayor",
    "numbers": [8, 35, 15, 22, 18],
    "correct_answer": [8, 15, 18, 22, 35],
    "symbol": "<"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [53, 14, 32, 7, 19],
    "correct_answer": [53, 32, 19, 14, 7],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [40, 30, 55, 10, 25],
    "correct_answer": [55, 40, 30, 25, 10],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [77, 50, 88, 23, 31],
    "correct_answer": [88, 77, 50, 31, 23],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [80, 58, 90, 12, 45],
    "correct_answer": [90, 80, 58, 45, 12],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [21, 41, 18, 5, 27],
    "correct_answer": [41, 27, 21, 18, 5],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [64, 69, 42, 37, 81],
    "correct_answer": [81, 69, 64, 42, 37],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [36, 56, 44, 29, 71],
    "correct_answer": [71, 56, 44, 36, 29],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [57, 11, 63, 8, 22],
    "correct_answer": [63, 57, 22, 11, 8],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [10, 1, 9, 6, 3],
    "correct_answer": [10, 9, 6, 3, 1],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [54, 57, 29, 32, 45],
    "correct_answer": [57, 54, 45, 32, 29],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [30, 25, 60, 15, 20],
    "correct_answer": [60, 30, 25, 20, 15],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [92, 59, 88, 40, 75],
    "correct_answer": [92, 88, 75, 59, 40],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [35, 77, 66, 22, 55],
    "correct_answer": [77, 66, 55, 35, 22],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [53, 59, 41, 33, 70],
    "correct_answer": [70, 59, 53, 41, 33],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [8, 64, 25, 47, 12],
    "correct_answer": [64, 47, 25, 12, 8],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [59, 14, 22, 11, 30],
    "correct_answer": [59, 30, 22, 14, 11],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [66, 54, 38, 19, 25],
    "correct_answer": [66, 54, 38, 25, 19],
    "symbol": ">"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordena estos numeros de mayor a menor",
    "numbers": [8, 35, 15, 22, 18],
    "correct_answer": [35, 22, 18, 15, 8],
    "symbol": ">"
  }
]
